discovertheforest.org 2017-08-16

# Discover The Forest

## Privacy

THIS IS OUR OFFICIAL PRIVACY POLICY, WHICH IS PART OF OUR TERMS OF USE AND FORMS A PART OF YOUR LEGAL AGREEMENT WITH US. PLEASE READ IT CAREFULLY SINCE IT DESCRIBES THE TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION, THE CIRCUMSTANCES IN WHICH WE DISCLOSE OR SHARE INFORMATION AND HOW YOU CAN ACCESS, UPDATE OR DELETE CERTAIN INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED ABOUT YOU, OR, IF YOU HAVE CONSENTED, YOUR CHILD IF THEY ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OLD (REFERRED TO INDIVIDUALLY AND/OR COLLECTIVELY AS "YOU"). 

**Any terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in ourTerms of Use.**

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE COLLECT IT

When you access or visit any of our Websites, we and our operational service providers and others who host our Websites often use technology that can recognize, collect and/or transmit information that is associated with you, but which do not personally identify you. Although the term "cookie" specifically refers to a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes, we will use the term "cookie" to refer generically to any technology that can recognize, collect and/or transmit information about your visits to our Websites. This type of information includes such data as the Internet or web domain that referred you, the type of operating system and browser you are using, the date and time of your visit, data relating to activities on our Websites (e.g., so-called ‘clickstream' data) and other technological attributes about your visit to our Websites. This information is used to analyze trends, administer our Websites, track user movements on our Websites, and gather aggregate demographic information about visitors so we can continually improve our Websites.   
Cookies also allow our Websites to recognize a users' computer or access device each time it is used to visit a particular Website and cookies can keep count of how often you return. Cookies can also track how you use our Websites, your preferences for features and functions and, for Websites that have registration or similar features, cookies can store information such as your user name and password so you don't have to re-enter them each time you return to visit. Cookies don't personally identify you or any particular user or individual.   
You can disable or turn the cookie feature off by changing the settings on your Internet browser and you can also change the settings to stop your browser from automatically accepting cookies. Although changing these settings may not affect your ability to browse, it may affect your ability to use certain features and functions of our Websites and it may also require you to re-enter certain information each time you visit or attempt to use our Websites. You should consult the operating instructions that apply to your browser to determine how to best configure your browser settings for your needs.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use the term "Personal Information" to refer to any information you provide in connection with your use of any of our Websites by which you can be personally identified. Personal Information may include such things as your name, street address, telephone number, date of birth, e-mail address and any other information which might reasonably be used to identify you. We only obtain Personal Information from you when you submit it to us or provide it on one or more of our Websites that require it in order to allow you to register, subscribe or take advantage of certain features, functions, services, activities, promotions and content on our Websites (these are referred to as "Content" in our Terms of Use). You may also email us with a question or for more information and we will use your contact information (which includes Personal Information such as an email address) to help us respond and for customer service purposes. Unless you voluntary provide or send us Personal Information, we will always ask you to submit or provide it to us before collecting your Personal Information, although you may not be able to use the particular Content, if you choose not to provide your Personal Information. If you provide or submit your Personal Information to any of our Websites, we will always give you the right to review, update and/or delete your Personal Information, subject to our obligations to comply with legal, regulatory our internal audit and record-keeping requirements. 

### Sponsors, advertisers and other third parties

Our Websites may contain or display information from our sponsors, advertisers, operational service providers (see Disclosure to Third Parties below) or others (each, a "Third Party") that offer to make information, goods or services available, provide opportunities to participate in promotions or engage in activities or that link or redirect your browser to other websites, materials or organizations. We may also use Third Parties to display or serve advertising on our Websites, as well as for distributing our online, email, messaged or web-based newsletters and other information. Third Parties often also employ cookies to measure advertising effectiveness. You should be aware that even if you encounter an advertisement, link or reference to a Third Party website on one of our Websites and even if we have a relationship with them, we do not control them, their websites or their policies and practices regarding use of their websites or any rules they have regarding the use of cookies or collection, use or disclosure of your information (including Personal Information). These are within their control and not ours and the terms and conditions, as well as the privacy policies that apply to these Third Parties and their websites are their responsibility, not ours. 

### Disclosure to Third Parties

We do not sell, rent, lease, provide or otherwise disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated entities unless the Supplemental Privacy Policy that applies to your use of a particular Website. We will always let you know if we intend to provide any of your Personal Information to a Third Party, you will always have an opportunity to read and review the Supplemental Privacy Policy that applies and we will ask you to consent ("Opt in") whenever we intend to do so.   
We always have the right to disclose your Personal Information to any Third Party we engage for the purpose of administering, operating, configuring site design, maintaining and providing internal support for our Websites and Content on our Websites. These Third Parties are called operational service providers that provide internal support to operations and activities and/or for Site design, development, hosting and operations. We always request that our operational service providers protect your privacy and not disclose your Personal Information to third party marketers that are not associated with our Websites, nor are they permitted to use your Personal Information for their own marketing or promotional purposes.

We also reserve the right to make your Personal Information available:

  * When we are compelled by a governmental agency, law, regulation, a court or other legal process; 
  * If we believe you are, have or may violate any law, regulation, our Terms of Use;
  * If we believe you are or may be a threat to safety, property, interests or rights of us or others;
  * In order to investigate, respond to or resolve problems or inquiries or defend our interests;
  * In a merger, acquisition, change of control, joint venture or other business combination.

You should also be aware we are public service organization and simply because a website or web page includes our logo, name or otherwise refers to us, does not mean the website or web page is ours or under our control. We work with sponsors, advertisers and government agencies to bring you public service advertising and if you enter, provide or submit Personal Information on or to a co-branded website or web page you may be subject to the terms, conditions and privacy policies of the Third Party sponsor, advertiser, government agency or co-branding organization.

#### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We only use information that we collect or obtain when you use our Websites as described in this Privacy Policy, for our internal research purposes or to ensure compliance with our Terms of Use. If we or any of our Websites collect, maintain, use or intend to share your Personal Information for other purposes than as described in this Privacy Policy, we will ensure that is included within the Supplemental Privacy Policy that applies to the Website or Websites involved. 

### Security

We maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality. We also try to limit information access to individuals who need to have such access to perform their responsibilities associated with our Websites and the Content on our Websites. Any employee found violating our standards of security and confidentiality is subject to our disciplinary processes. We request our operational service providers to follow the same policy. The Internet, however, and communications cannot be guaranteed to be secure and it is possible that others may unlawfully intercept or access information, transmissions or communications to, from or within our Websites. 

#### YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING Personal Information.

In addition to any terms, conditions or rights that are described in any Supplemental Privacy Policy applicable to particular Websites, you always have the right to request that: (i) we correct or update your Personal Information; (ii) we not share your Personal Information with third parties; or (iii) your Personal Information be removed from our active marketing databases. Although we will usually provide you with the ability to update or delete Personal Information directly online, some Personal Information may not be changed or deleted by you and requires you to contact us for verification (e.g., birth date, email address, name). The Supplemental Privacy Policy that applies to the Website will provide you with the email address or contact information that applies to that Website so that you can contact us with a request to change that type of information. 

#### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a resident of the State of California, under the California Civil Code, you have the right to request information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options from companies conducting business in California. For each Website that collects or obtains any Personal Information from you, our Supplemental Privacy Policy will provide you details, as well as contact information for the Privacy Administrator for that Website and specifics regarding how to send us a request for information. All requests sent via postal mail must be labeled "Your California Privacy Rights" on the envelope or post card and clearly stated on the actual request. We will not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile and we are not responsible for requests that are not labeled, are not sent properly, or that do not have complete information. 

#### CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We can change this Privacy Policy at any time (see our Terms of Use). As with our Terms of Use, we encourage you to come back and review this Privacy Policy often to be sure you are aware of the terms, conditions, rights and obligations that apply to you. 

#### CONTACT US

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy that applies to any of our Websites, first check to see if that Website has a Supplemental Privacy Policy with contact information if you have questions about that Website. For general questions about our Privacy Policies please email us at [webmaster@adcouncil.org](mailto:webmaster@adcouncil.org) or write us to the attention of our Privacy Administrator, at The Advertising Council, 815 Second Ave., New York, NY 10017, and please specify if you are inquiring about a specific Website to help us better assist and respond to your questions.

#### REGISTERING FOR OUR WEBSITES

In order to obtain Services from some of our Websites, you will need to enroll on or with that Website through a registration process. You will be required to provide us with certain information about you during the registration process and in order to allow us to give you access to Services generally not available to others, you will also be required to choose a user name and password (or we may assign an initial password, which we will give you the option to change after you register). Once we confirm we have received all the information required for registration we will confirm that you have become a "Registered User" of that Website and you will need to log in to that Website using your unique user name and password combination which we will refer to as your User ID.  
Unless we indicate otherwise during the registration process for any particular Website, you must live in the United States and either be at least 13 years old, or provide verifiable adult consent in advance from a parent or legal guardian ("parent") to use the Services associated with that particular Website. If you are at least 13 years old, but you are not yet considered an adult where you live (generally age 18) you can only enroll and become a Registered User if you get consent from your parent. If you are under 13, and have not provided advance verifiable consent from a parent, you may not enroll, register, become a Registered User or use our Services at all.

#### KEEPING YOUR PASSWORD SAFE

Your User ID is personal and you must keep it strictly confidential. Don't give it to anyone or allow others to use it because you are solely responsible for anything and everything that can be connected to, associated with or traced to your User ID, including, without limitation, any and all fees, costs and charges, liability and damages. You agree to immediately notify us if you become aware or believe there is or may have been any unauthorized use of your user name or password or any other need to deactivate your User ID due to security concerns. You, not us, are solely responsible and liable for the use of your User ID by you or anyone else and you will defend and indemnify us as described in the section of our Terms of Use entitled "You Are Indemnifying Us" for any damage or harm resulting from your User ID. 

#### TERMINATION OF YOUR REGISTRATION

You can terminate your registration on any of our Websites by following the instructions we provide on that Website, subject to any particular obligations you previously agreed to and which have not yet been fully performed, fulfilled or completed. We may terminate your use of and registration on any of our Websites, at any time without any liability or further obligation of any kind whatsoever to you or any other party.

Copyright © 2014  
All Rights Reserved
